Is this the face of a terrorist?
Miral is a drama, history film directed by Julian Schnabel.
A drama centered on an orphaned Palestinian girl growing up in the wake of the
first Arab-Israeli war who finds herself drawn into the conflict.
Miral, played by Freida Pinto.
Hidi Husseini, played by Hiam Abbass.
Eddie, played by Willem Dafoe.
Bertha Spafford, played by Vanessa Redgrave.
Interrogating Officer, played by Uri Gavriel.
Jamal, played by Alexander Siddig.
Miral is a 2010 biographical political film directed by Julian Schnabel about the coming of age of a Palestinian girl
named Miral who grows up in the wake of the 1948 Arab–Israeli War and finds herself drawn into the conflict.
The screenplay was written by Rula Jebreal, based on her novel of the same name.
The film was released on 3 September at the 2010 Venice Film
Festival and on 15 September 2010 in France.
The film explores themes of palestine, based on novel or book, based on
memoir or autobiography, arab–israeli war (1948), west bank.
The tone is emotional.